const data = {
    past: {
        questions: [
            {
                question: "John was so thirsty that he ____ two glasses of water.",
                answers: ["drinked", "drank", "drink", "had drunk"],
                validAnswer: 2,
            },
            {
                question: "Nobody ___ while we were having dinner",
                answers: ["didn`t phone", "did phone", "phoned", "had phoned"],
                validAnswer: 3,
            },
            {
                question: "When I got home, my sister ___ with a kitten.",
                answers: ["was playing", "playing", "were playing", "played"],
                validAnswer: 1,
            },
            {
                question: "We ___ dinner before our parents ___",
                answers: ["had had, arrived", "had, arrived", "had, had arrived", "had, arrive"],
                validAnswer: 1,
            },
            {
                question: "They told me that he ___ in this company for more than 30 years!",
                answers: ["worked", "had worked", "has been working", "had been working"],
                validAnswer: 4,
            },
            {
                question: "We ___ tea when our grandparents came.",
                answers: ["were having", "were have", "was having", "was have"],
                validAnswer: 1,
            },
            {
                question: "I ___ my project by 3 o’clock yesterday.",
                answers: ["had finish", "had finished", "finished", "finish"],
                validAnswer: 2,
            },
            {
                question: "It was my brother`s birthday on Sunday, so I ___ him a postcard.",
                answers: ["sent", "send", "have sent", "sended"],
                validAnswer: 1,
            },
            {
                question: "What ___ ? You looked so tired.",
                answers: ["had been you doing", "had you been doing", "had been doing you", "you had been doing"],
                validAnswer: 2,
            },
            {
                question: "We ___ last night due to the nasty weather.",
                answers: ["did go out", "didn`t went out", "didn`t go out", "did went out"],
                validAnswer: 3,
            },
            {
                question: "We ___ a New Year tree all morning yesrerday.",
                answers: ["were to decorating", "was decorating", "were decorating", "decorated"],
                validAnswer: 3,
            },
            {
                question: "I ___ out that I ___ the exam.",
                answers: ["had found, didn’t pass", "had found, hadn’t passed", "found, hadn’t passed", "had founded, didn`t pass"],
                validAnswer: 3,
            },
            {
                question: "I ___ in a flat for 30 years before I moved to a house.",
                answers: ["had live", "Тhad been living", "had lived", "was living"],
                validAnswer: 2,
            },
            {
                question: "Mary ___ home when she met her old friend.",
                answers: ["were walking", "was walk", "was walking", "walked"],
                validAnswer: 3,
            },
            {
                question: "He ___ it secret that he ___ a bicycle for his son.",
                answers: ["keep, had bought", "kept, had bought", "kept, bought", "keeped, had bought"],
                validAnswer: 2,
            },
            {
                question: "It ___ all night so I had to dig out my car in the morning.",
                answers: ["had snowed", "has been snowing", "was snowing", "had been snowing"],
                validAnswer: 4,
            },
        ]
    },
    present: {
        questions: [
            {
                question: "They ___ orange juice.",
                answers: ["drinks", "doesn`t drink", "doesn`t drinks", "drink"],
                validAnswer: 4,
            },
            {
                question: "I ___ for Christine. Do you know where she is?",
                answers: ["am looking", "are looking", "is looking", "look"],
                validAnswer: 1,
            },
            {
                question: "How long ___ singing lessons?",
                answers: ["you have been taking", "has you been taking", "have you been taking", "been have you taking"],
                validAnswer: 3,
            },
            {
                question: "Nick ___ a live football match before.",
                answers: ["have never seen", "has never seen", "hasn’t never seen", "has seen never"],
                validAnswer: 2,
            },
            {
                question: "It ___ dark. Shall I turn on the light?",
                answers: ["are getting", "am getting", "get", "is getting"],
                validAnswer: 4,
            },
            {
                question: "A pianist ___ the piano.",
                answers: ["play", "plays", "doesn`t plays", "don`t play"],
                validAnswer: 2,
            },
            {
                question: "Lena ___ geometry since she was 30.",
                answers: ["has been teaching", "has teaching", "teaches", "have been"],
                validAnswer: 1,
            },
            {
                question: "Have you got an umbrella? It ___ to rain.",
                answers: ["is starting", "starts", "am starting", "are starting"],
                validAnswer: 1,
            },
            {
                question: "My wife ___ invitations for the party.",
                answers: ["have already sent", "has already sent", "has already send", "has sent already"],
                validAnswer: 2,
            },
            {
                question: "Mary and Sue ___ to the cinema.",
                answers: ["goes", "doesn`t go", "doesn`t goes", "don`t go"],
                validAnswer: 4,
            },
            {
                question: "Donna ___ for a job for half a year.",
                answers: ["has looking", "have been looking", "look", "has been looking"],
                validAnswer: 4,
            },
            {
                question: "Why are all these people here? What ___ ?",
                answers: ["are happening", "is happening", "am happening", "happens"],
                validAnswer: 2,
            },
            {
                question: "Are you going anywhere this summer? Yes, we ___ a trip to Italy.",
                answers: ["have book", "has booked", "have booked", "book"],
                validAnswer: 3,
            },
            {
                question: "Mark ... cakes.",
                answers: ["don't love", "doesn't love", "love", "doesn't loves"],
                validAnswer: 2,
            },
            {
                question: "Brian ___ his new project yet.",
                answers: ["not started", "haven’t started", "hasn’t started", "doesn`t start"],
                validAnswer: 3,
            },
            {
                question: "The baby ___ for three hours.",
                answers: ["been sleeping", "has been sleeping", "have been sleeping", "sleeps"],
                validAnswer: 2,
            },
        ]
    },
    future: {
        questions: [
            {
                question: "He ___ to the cinema tomorrow.",
                answers: ["go not will", "will not go", "will go not", "go"],
                validAnswer: 2,
            },
            {
                question: "В каком варианте глагол to stay правильно оформлен во времени Future Perfect Continuous?",
                answers: ["will have been staying", "will have being staying", "will have being stayed", "will have been stay"],
                validAnswer: 1,
            },
            {
                question: "I ___ this book by next week.",
                answers: ["will not read", "won’t had read", "will not have read", "will no had read"],
                validAnswer: 3,
            },
            {
                question: "What ___ after work?",
                answers: ["will he do", "do will he", "do", "he will do"],
                validAnswer: 1,
            },
            {
                question: " I ___ during rush hour.",
                answers: ["will be driving", "will have drive", "will be drive", "will have driving"],
                validAnswer: 1,
            },
            {
                question: "At the end of this school year, she ____ for 51 years. ",
                answers: ["will teaching", "will have teaching", "will been teaching", "will have been teaching"],
                validAnswer: 4,
            },
            {
                question: "At noon tomorrow, I ________ on a beach somewhere.",
                answers: ["'ll be relaxing", "relax", "relax", "will being relax"],
                validAnswer: 1,
            },
            {
                question: "Tennis fans ___ at Wimbledon all day to buy tickets.",
                answers: ["will have being queueing", "will have been queue", "will been have queueing", "will have been queueing"],
                validAnswer: 4,
            },
            {
                question: "He will not be ___ the bus today.",
                answers: ["take", "taken", "take", "taking"],
                validAnswer: 4,
            },
            {
                question: "I ___ all my exams by 15 June. ",
                answers: ["will have pass", "will have passed", "will pass", "will passed"],
                validAnswer: 2,
            },
            {
                question: "We ___ an English lesson on Friday.",
                answers: ["have", "not will have", "will have not", "won’t have"],
                validAnswer: 4,
            },
            {
                question: "He ___ playing football by 3 o’clock tomorrow.",
                answers: ["will have finished", "will finish", "will has finished", "will finish"],
                validAnswer: 1,
            },
            {
                question: "Where ___ sleeping?",
                answers: ["you be", "will you", "will you be", "you will"],
                validAnswer: 3,
            },
            {
                question: "Alice ___ dinner by 7 o’clock tomorrow. ",
                answers: ["will have cooked", "will has cooked", "will cooked", "will cook"],
                validAnswer: 1,
            },
            {
                question: "She ___ the movie tonight.",
                answers: ["watch will", "will watch", "watch’ll", "watch"],
                validAnswer: 2,
            },
            {
                question: "Next year I ___ in the company for 30 years.",
                answers: ["will have being working", "will have been working", "will have working", "will have work"],
                validAnswer: 2,
            },
        ]
    }
};

export default data;